[{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14078,"timeElapsed":169806},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664190814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6672,"timeElapsed":176481},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5754,"timeElapsed":182236},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":13965,"timeElapsed":196203},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":10233,"timeElapsed":206438},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":11008,"timeElapsed":217448},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664238080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6295,"timeElapsed":223747},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5960,"timeElapsed":229710},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":232471},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10071,"timeElapsed":244612},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664261568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2621,"timeElapsed":247235},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4202,"timeElapsed":251439},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3804,"timeElapsed":255245},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1974,"timeElapsed":257221},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664275963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4405,"timeElapsed":261630},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1290,"timeElapsed":262922},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4203,"timeElapsed":267127},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1515,"timeElapsed":268645},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7325,"timeElapsed":277709},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2497,"timeElapsed":280208},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664301438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6895,"timeElapsed":287105},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2977,"timeElapsed":290084},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1795,"timeElapsed":291882},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2703,"timeElapsed":294587},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664310552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1629,"timeElapsed":296219},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":299063},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1666,"timeElapsed":300732},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":13132,"timeElapsed":315825},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664332298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2139,"timeElapsed":317965},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664334978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2677,"timeElapsed":320645},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":15674,"timeElapsed":336320},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664352745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2090,"timeElapsed":338411},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1906,"timeElapsed":340320},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1715,"timeElapsed":342037},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2348,"timeElapsed":344388},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1346,"timeElapsed":345736},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7073,"timeElapsed":353991},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2455,"timeElapsed":356448},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2432,"timeElapsed":358882},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":361945},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1564,"timeElapsed":363510},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1419,"timeElapsed":364931},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1567,"timeElapsed":366501},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2042,"timeElapsed":368546},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1588,"timeElapsed":370136},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6297,"timeElapsed":377786},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":379874},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664396753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":382420},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":6879,"timeElapsed":389302},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":392326},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664408194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1532,"timeElapsed":393861},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1468,"timeElapsed":395332},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664411551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1883,"timeElapsed":397218},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1420,"timeElapsed":398640},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664420680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6285,"timeElapsed":406347},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1855,"timeElapsed":408205},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664424993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2452,"timeElapsed":410659},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":412793},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1329,"timeElapsed":414125},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1333,"timeElapsed":415461},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664438488,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8693,"timeElapsed":424155},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3763,"timeElapsed":427919},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664444279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":429946},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2252,"timeElapsed":432199},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5699,"timeElapsed":439179},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3255,"timeElapsed":442436},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664458941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2170,"timeElapsed":444608},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664463925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":449592},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664465127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1199,"timeElapsed":450794},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1317,"timeElapsed":452113},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1285,"timeElapsed":453401},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664475240,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7504,"timeElapsed":460907},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664479063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":464729},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664482350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":468017},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6418,"timeElapsed":476039},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2033,"timeElapsed":478074},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664494215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":479882},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2316,"timeElapsed":482200},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664497692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1156,"timeElapsed":483359},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664500733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3038,"timeElapsed":486400},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3538,"timeElapsed":489939},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664506240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1966,"timeElapsed":491907},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664508087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1844,"timeElapsed":493753},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7620,"timeElapsed":504253},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3449,"timeElapsed":507704},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664524297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2259,"timeElapsed":509964},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7388,"timeElapsed":517354},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1483,"timeElapsed":518839},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664534832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1657,"timeElapsed":520499},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664536472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1638,"timeElapsed":522139},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1941,"timeElapsed":524083},{"subjectID":"etr0vgav8j","prolificID":"6682a9a3ff9dc00969537ae3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421616b54385725652927","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2123,"timeElapsed":526209}]